var quizArray = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of the duel that gives you a sword, a bow and arrows, and a rod?",
        options: ["UHC", "Classic", "Bridge", "Bedwars"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "Which Arcade Game on Hypixel is based of off Withers?",
        options: ["Ender Spleef", "Party Games", "Mini Walls", "Build Battle"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "After the 1.9 update, what weapon takes the longest to recharge?",
        options: ["Axe", "Shovel", "Sword", "Pickaxe"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "What is the common nickname for an Enchanted Golden Apple?",
        options: ["God Apple", "Gapple", "Super Gapple", "EG"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "What is the fastest form of bridging possible (without hacks)?",
        options: ["Godbridge", "Moonwalk", "Speed Bridge", "Speed Telly"],
        answer: 3
    },{
        question: "Which version has sword blocking?",
        options: ["1.12", "1.9", "1.8", "1.19"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "What modes can improve your bridging?",
        options: ["Bedwars", "Skywars", "Duels", "All of the Above"],
        answer: 3
    },{
        question: "What clicking method gets the most CPS (with double clicks)?",
        options: ["Single Clicking", "Butterfly Clicking", "Drag Clicking", "Jitter Clicking"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "What is the most popular boxing server on the planet?",
        options: ["Hypixel", "Minemen", "Muffinized", "Ghostly"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "Will you subscribe to my Youtube channel?(https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCg3e1wxLK6v_XlFXxSRNLow)",
        options: ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Idk"],
        answer: 0
    }
];